Country Code	Region	IncomeGroup	SpecialNotes	TableName
ABW	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Aruba
AFE			"26 countries, stretching from the Red Sea in the North to the Cape of Good Hope in the South (https://www.worldbank.org/en/region/afr/eastern-and-southern-africa)"	Africa Eastern and Southern
AFG	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Low income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: March 20). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY).

In addition, the World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1960-2006. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Afghanistan
AFW			"22 countries, stretching from the westernmost point of Africa, across the equator, and partly along the Atlantic Ocean till the Republic of Congo in the South (https://www.worldbank.org/en/region/afr/western-and-central-africa)"	Africa Western and Central
AGO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1994-2024. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Angola
ALB	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Albania
AND	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Andorra
ARB			Arab World aggregate. Arab World is composed of members of the League of Arab States.	Arab World
ARE	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		United Arab Emirates
ARG	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1971-2018. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Argentina
ARM	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Armenia
ASM	East Asia & Pacific	High income		American Samoa
ATG	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Antigua and Barbuda
AUS	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Australia
AUT	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 13.7603 Austrian schilling. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Austria
AZE	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Azerbaijan
BDI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1983-2024. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Burundi
BEL	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 40.3399 Belgian franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Belgium
BEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Benin
BFA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Burkina Faso
BGD	South Asia	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Bangladesh
BGR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Bulgaria
BHR	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		Bahrain
BHS	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		"Bahamas, The"
BIH	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Bosnia and Herzegovina
BLR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Data before 2015 were adjusted to reflect the new denomination effective from July 1, 2016 (BYN), a decrease of 10,000 times (1 BYN = 10,000 BYR)"	Belarus
BLZ	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Belize
BMU	North America	High income		Bermuda
BOL	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income		Bolivia
BRA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Brazil
BRB	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Barbados
BRN	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Brunei Darussalam
BTN	South Asia	Lower middle income		Bhutan
BWA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Botswana
CAF	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Central African Republic
CAN	North America	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Canada
CEB			Central Europe and the Baltics aggregate.	Central Europe and the Baltics
CHE	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Switzerland
CHI	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Channel Islands
CHL	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Chile
CHN	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"On 1 July 1997 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Hong Kong, and on 20 December 1999, China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Macao. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China.

The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1978-1993. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	China
CIV	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Côte d'Ivoire
CMR	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Cameroon
COD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1999-2004. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	"Congo, Dem. Rep."
COG	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		"Congo, Rep."
COL	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Colombia
COM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Comoros
CPV	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Cabo Verde
CRI	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Costa Rica
CSS			Caribbean small states aggregate.	Caribbean small states
CUB	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Cuba
CUW	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Curaçao
CYM	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Cayman Islands
CYP	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2008: 1 euro = 0.585274 Cyprus pounds. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Cyprus
CZE	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Czechia
DEU	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 1.95583 Deutsche Mark. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Germany
DJI	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income		Djibouti
DMA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Dominica
DNK	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Denmark
DOM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Dominican Republic
DZA	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Upper middle income		Algeria
EAP				East Asia & Pacific (excluding high income)
EAR			Early-dividend countries are mostly lower-middle-income countries further along the fertility transition. Fertility rates have fallen below four births per woman and the working-age share of the population is likely rising considerably.	Early-demographic dividend
EAS			East Asia and Pacific regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	East Asia & Pacific
ECA				Europe & Central Asia (excluding high income)
ECS			Europe and Central Asia regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	Europe & Central Asia
ECU	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Ecuador
EGY	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30) for the years 1980 and after. The data from 1973 to 1979 refer to the calendar year data. Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY). 

In addition, the World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1965-2021. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors.

The national accounts data for Egypt has been updated to reflect local constant prices in the year 2022, moving from the previous reference of 2017."	"Egypt, Arab Rep."
EMU			Euro area aggregate.	Euro area
ERI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1992-1997. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Eritrea
ESP	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 166.386 Spanish peseta. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Spain
EST	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2011: 1 euro = 15.6466 Estonian kroon. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Estonia
ETH	Sub-Saharan Africa		"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: July 7). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Ethiopia
EUU			European Union aggregate.	European Union
FCS			"Fragile and conflict-affected situations aggregate as of FY25 (July 1, 2024-June 30, 2025). Countries are distinguished based on the nature and severity of issues they face and classified into two categories: (i) Countries with significant institutional and social fragility, determined by indicators of policy quality and fragility. (ii) Countries experiencing violent conflict, classified by conflict-related deaths per capita and further divided into high-intensity and medium-intensity conflict subcategories. For more information, please visit https://www.worldbank.org/en/topic/fragilityconflictviolence/brief/classification-of-fragile-and-conflict-affected-situations."	Fragile and conflict affected situations
FIN	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 5.94573 Finnish markka. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Finland
FJI	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		Fiji
FRA	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 6.55957 French franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	France
FRO	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Faroe Islands
FSM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. The source for national accounts data is the Pacific and Virgin Islands Training Initiative.	"Micronesia, Fed. Sts."
GAB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Gabon
GBR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		United Kingdom
GEO	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Includes self-governed areas only, which mostly exclude Abkhazia and South Ossetia, but small areas in Abkhazia and South Ossetia are included before 2008 or 2009 because of the changes in self-governed areas."	Georgia
GHA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1974-1987. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Ghana
GIB	Europe & Central Asia	High income	The DEC conversion is not reported when national accounts data are unavailable.	Gibraltar
GIN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Guinea
GMB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		"Gambia, The"
GNB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Guinea-Bissau
GNQ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Equatorial Guinea
GRC	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 340.75 Greek drachma. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Greece
GRD	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Grenada
GRL	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Greenland
GTM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1985-2003. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Guatemala
GUM	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Guam
GUY	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Guyana
HIC			"High income group aggregate. High-income economies are those in which 2024 Atlas GNI per capita was more than $13,935."	High income
HKG	East Asia & Pacific	High income	"On 1 July 1997 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Hong Kong. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China. Agriculture value added includes mining and quarrying."	"Hong Kong SAR, China"
HND	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1988-1989. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Honduras
HPC			"The Heavily Indebted Poor Countries (HIPC) Initiative, launched in 1996 by the IMF and World Bank, aims to reduce the external debt burdens of the most indebted poor countries. Most participants have completed the program, receiving a total of $76 billion in debt-service relief. For more information, visit https://www.imf.org/en/About/Factsheets/Sheets/2016/08/01/16/11/Debt-Relief-Under-the-Heavily-Indebted-Poor-Countries-Initiative. Data presented are aggregates for HIPC countries."	Heavily indebted poor countries (HIPC)
HRV	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2023: 1 euro = 7.53450 Croatian kuna. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Croatia
HTI	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: September 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Haiti
HUN	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Hungary
IBD			IBRD only group aggregate.	IBRD only
IBT			"IDA and IBRD total group aggregate (includes IDA only, IDA blend, and IBRD only)."	IDA & IBRD total
IDA			IDA total group aggregate (includes IDA only and IDA blend).	IDA total
IDB			IDA blend group aggregate.	IDA blend
IDN	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Data for Indonesia include Timor-Leste through 1999 unless otherwise noted.	Indonesia
IDX			IDA only group aggregate.	IDA only
IMN	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"Classification for years after 2012 was adjusted and figures were re-estimated by the World Bank, based on the detailed data published by the Cabinet Office, and are not consistent with data for 2011 and before."	Isle of Man
IND	South Asia	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: March 31). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	India
IRL	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 0.787564 Irish pound. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Ireland
IRN	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Upper middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: March 20). Also, the World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to 1972-2024. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	"Iran, Islamic Rep."
IRQ	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Upper middle income		Iraq
ISL	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Iceland
ISR	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		Israel
ITA	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 1936.27 Italian lira. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Italy
JAM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Jamaica
JOR	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income		Jordan
JPN	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Japan
KAZ	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Kazakhstan
KEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Kenya
KGZ	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Kyrgyz Republic
KHM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1963-2004. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Cambodia
KIR	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Kiribati
KNA	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		St. Kitts and Nevis
KOR	East Asia & Pacific	High income		"Korea, Rep."
KWT	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		Kuwait
LAC				Latin America & Caribbean (excluding high income)
LAO	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1960-2020. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Lao PDR
LBN	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1984-2024. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Lebanon
LBR	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	National accounts data are provided in the US dollar.	Liberia
LBY	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Upper middle income		Libya
LCA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		St. Lucia
LCN				Latin America & Caribbean
LDC				Least developed countries: UN classification
LIC			"Low income group aggregate. Low-income economies are those in which 2024 Atlas GNI per capita was $1,135 or less."	Low income
LIE	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Liechtenstein
LKA	South Asia	Lower middle income		Sri Lanka
LMC			"Lower middle income group aggregate. Lower-middle-income economies are those in which Atlas 2024 GNI per capita was between $1,136 and $4,495."	Lower middle income
LMY			"Low and middle-income group aggregate. Low and middle-income economies are those in which Atlas 2024 GNI per capita was less than $13,935."	Low & middle income
LSO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Lesotho
LTE			Late-dividend countries are mostly upper middle-income countries. Fertility rates are typically above replacement levels of 2.1 births per woman but continue to decline with shrinking working-age shares and rapid aging.	Late-demographic dividend
LTU	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2015: 1 euro = 3.45280 Lithuanian litas. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Lithuania
LUX	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 40.3399 Luxembourg franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Luxembourg
LVA	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2014: 1 euro = 0.702804 Latvian lats. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries. Based on data from EUROSTAT, the new reference year is 2010."	Latvia
MAC	East Asia & Pacific	High income	"On 20 December 1999 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Macao. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China."	"Macao SAR, China"
MAF	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		St. Martin (French part)
MAR	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income		Morocco
MCO	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Monaco
MDA	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Excluding Transnistria. For 1950-94, World Bank estimates using UN World Population Prospects' growth rates of whole Moldova."	Moldova
MDG	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Madagascar
MDV	South Asia	Upper middle income		Maldives
MEA			"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan regional aggregate (including all income levels). Since July 1, 2025, Afghanistan and Pakistan are classified as part of the Middle East and North Africa region, moving them from South Asia."	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"
MEX	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		Mexico
MHL	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Marshall Islands
MIC			"Middle income group aggregate. Middle-income economies are those in which 2024 Atlas GNI per capita was between $1,136 and $13,935."	Middle income
MKD	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		North Macedonia
MLI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Mali
MLT	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2008: 1 euro = 0.4293 Maltese lira. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries. National accounts data source from 1995 to 2015 is Eurostat; prior to 1995 is UN."	Malta
MMR	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: September 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY). 	  

In addition, the World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1960-2014. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Myanmar
MNA			"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan regional aggregate (excluding high-income economies). Since July 1, 2025, Afghanistan and Pakistan are classified as part of the Middle East and North Africa region, moving them from South Asia."	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan (excluding high income)"
MNE	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Montenegro declared independence from Serbia and Montenegro on June 3, 2006. Where available, data for each country are shown separately. However, for Serbia, some indicators continue to include data for Montenegro through 2005."	Montenegro
MNG	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1991-2004. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Mongolia
MNP	East Asia & Pacific	High income		Northern Mariana Islands
MOZ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Mozambique
MRT	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	National account data were adjusted to reflect the new banknote (1 new ouguiya = 10 old ouguiya)	Mauritania
MUS	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income		Mauritius
MWI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Malawi
MYS	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		Malaysia
NAC			North America regional aggregate. There are no economies in North America classified as low or middle-income.	North America
NAM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Namibia
NCL	East Asia & Pacific	High income		New Caledonia
NER	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Niger
NGA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to 1970-2020. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Nigeria
NIC	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1988-2006. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Nicaragua
NLD	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 2.20371 Netherlands guilder. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Netherlands
NOR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Norway
NPL	South Asia	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: July 14). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Nepal
NRU	East Asia & Pacific	High income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Nauru
NZL	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	New Zealand
OED				OECD members
OMN	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		Oman
OSS			Other small states aggregate.	Other small states
PAK	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Pakistan
PAN	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Panama
PER	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1988-2009. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Peru
PHL	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Philippines
PLW	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Palau
PNG	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Papua New Guinea
POL	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Poland
PRE			"Pre-dividend countries are mostly low-income countries, lagging in key human development indicators and with current fertility levels above four births per woman. They face very rapid population growth."	Pre-demographic dividend
PRI	Latin America & Caribbean	High income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.	Puerto Rico (US)
PRK	East Asia & Pacific	Low income		"Korea, Dem. People's Rep."
PRT	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 200.482 Portuguese escudo. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Portugal
PRY	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1982-1988. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors. Kindly note that GDP per capita and GNI per capita reported are calculated from the UN WPP data which likely creates discrepancy with the official per capita figures, calculated from the latest population census results."	Paraguay
PSE	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income	National accounts data are provided in the US dollar.	West Bank and Gaza
PSS			Pacific island small states aggregate.	Pacific island small states
PST			Post-dividend countries are mostly high-income countries where fertility has transitioned below replacement levels.	Post-demographic dividend
PYF	East Asia & Pacific	High income		French Polynesia
QAT	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		Qatar
ROU	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1987-1992. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Romania
RUS	Europe & Central Asia	High income		Russian Federation
RWA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Rwanda
SAS			"South Asia regional aggregate. Since July 1, 2025, Afghanistan and Pakistan are classified as part of the Middle East and North Africa region, moving them from South Asia. No economies in South Asia are classified as high-income."	South Asia
SAU	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	High income		Saudi Arabia
SDN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 2018-2020. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Sudan
SEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Senegal
SGP	East Asia & Pacific	High income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Singapore
SLB	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Solomon Islands
SLE	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Sierra Leone
SLV	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		El Salvador
SMR	Europe & Central Asia	High income		San Marino
SOM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 1977-2017. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Somalia
SRB	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Montenegro declared independence from Serbia and Montenegro on June 3, 2006. Where available, data for each country are shown separately. However, for Serbia, some indicators, such as those series for which data appear only for Serbia and not Montenegro--e.g., aid, environment, external debt, balance of payments, various social indicators excluding population--continue to include data for Montenegro through 2005. Moreover, data from 1999 onward for Serbia for most indicators exclude data for Kosovo, 1999 being the year when Kosovo became a territory under international administration pursuant to UN Security Council Resolution 1244 (1999); any exceptions are noted. Kosovo became a World Bank member on June 29, 2009; available data are shown separately for Kosovo. In 2011, the Statistical Office of Serbia improved the methodology of national accounts data for 2003 onward. Specifically, the classification of sectors was revised."	Serbia
SSA				Sub-Saharan Africa (excluding high income)
SSD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	South Sudan
SSF			Sub-Saharan Africa regional aggregate (includes all income levels).	Sub-Saharan Africa
SST			Small states aggregate.	Small states
STP	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	National account data were adjusted to reflect the new banknote (1 new Dobra STN = 1000 old Dobra STD)	São Tomé and Principe
SUR	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to 1989-2021. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Suriname
SVK	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2009: 1 euro = 30.126 Slovak koruna. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Slovak Republic
SVN	Europe & Central Asia	High income	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2007: 1 euro = 239.64 Slovenian tolar. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."	Slovenia
SWE	Europe & Central Asia	High income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Sweden
SWZ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Authorities revised national accounts from 1999 to 2015.	Eswatini
SXM	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Sint Maarten (Dutch part)
SYC	Sub-Saharan Africa	High income		Seychelles
SYR	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 2011-2024. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Syrian Arab Republic
TCA	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Turks and Caicos Islands
TCD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Chad
TEA			East Asia & Pacific (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	East Asia & Pacific (IDA & IBRD)
TEC			Europe & Central Asia (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Europe & Central Asia (IDA & IBRD)
TGO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income		Togo
THA	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	Thailand
TJK	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Tajikistan
TKM	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Turkmenistan
TLA			Latin America & the Caribbean (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Latin America & Caribbean (IDA & IBRD)
TLS	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Timor-Leste
TMN			"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan regional aggregate (IDA & IBRD countries). Since July 1, 2025, Afghanistan and Pakistan are classified as part of the Middle East and North Africa region, moving them from South Asia."	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan (IDA & IBRD)"
TON	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Tonga
TSA			"South Asia (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate. Since July 1, 2025, Afghanistan and Pakistan are classified as part of the Middle East and North Africa region, moving them from South Asia."	South Asia (IDA & IBRD)
TSS			Sub-Saharan Africa (IDA & IBRD countries) aggregate.	Sub-Saharan Africa (IDA & IBRD)
TTO	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Trinidad and Tobago
TUN	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Lower middle income		Tunisia
TUR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Türkiye
TUV	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income		Tuvalu
TZA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income		Tanzania
UGA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY). In addition, the World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to 1960-2009. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Uganda
UKR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Ukraine
UMC			"Upper middle income group aggregate. Upper-middle-income economies are those in which 2024 Atlas GNI per capita was between $4,496 and $13,935."	Upper middle income
URY	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Uruguay
USA	North America	High income		United States
UZB	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income		Uzbekistan
VCT	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income		St. Vincent and the Grenadines
VEN	Latin America & Caribbean			"Venezuela, RB"
VGB	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		British Virgin Islands
VIR	Latin America & Caribbean	High income		Virgin Islands (US)
VNM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Viet Nam
VUT	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income		Vanuatu
WLD				World
WSM	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"The reporting period for national accounts data is designated as either calendar year basis (CY) or fiscal year basis (FY). For this country, it is fiscal year-based (fiscal year-end: June 30). Also, an estimate (PA.NUS.ATLS) of the exchange rate covers the same period and thus differs from the official exchange rate (CY)."	Samoa
XKX	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income		Kosovo
YEM	"Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan & Pakistan"	Low income	"The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to 1990-2019. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	"Yemen, Rep."
ZAF	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.	South Africa
ZMB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"National accounts data were rebased to reflect the January 1, 2013, introduction of the new Zambian kwacha at a rate of 1,000 old kwacha = 1 new kwacha."	Zambia
ZWE	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"National Accounts data are reported in Zimbabwean Dollar (ZWL). Before 2017, one ZWL is set to be equal to one USD.

The World Bank systematically assesses the appropriateness of official exchange rates as conversion factors. In this country, multiple or dual exchange rate activity exists and must be accounted for appropriately in underlying statistics. An alternative estimate (“alternative conversion factor” - PA.NUS.ATLS) is thus calculated as a weighted average of the different exchange rates in use in the country. Doing so better reflects economic reality and leads to more accurate cross-country comparisons and country classifications by income level. For this country, this applies to the period 2017-2023. Alternative conversion factors are used in the Atlas methodology and elsewhere in World Development Indicators as single-year conversion factors."	Zimbabwe
